<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mobile on Arthur&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://arqueffe.github.io/tags/mobile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mobile on Arthur&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://arqueffe.github.io/tags/mobile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
      <title>Running ONNX Models in Flutter</title>
      <link>https://arqueffe.github.io/works/sentiment-v0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arqueffe.github.io/works/sentiment-v0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lately, I’ve been seeing a wave of articles and posts praising lightning-fast GPU inference. And don’t get me wrong, GPUs are great, and I absolutely appreciate a good speed boost as much as the next person. But I also believe a huge chunk of real-world use cases simply don’t need massive models or blazing inference speeds. In fact, for many apps, the ability to run small models fully offline, on the device that’s already in your pocket, provides far more practical value, especially when it comes to privacy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sentiment Analysis with BERT</title>
      <link>https://arqueffe.github.io/works/sentiment-v1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arqueffe.github.io/works/sentiment-v1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have got into the interest of porting NLP models to mobile devices, and I wanted to start somewhere. In parrallel, I have been trying to be more consistent with journaling, and it landed me exactly where I always start with a project. And so started my journey of investigating how to make a journaling app more engaging that just taking note. A first simple feature that could help is to track how you feel through the weeks, observe how things are going and evolving. This is where emotion classification comes in, and I wanted to see how I could do that on-device, without sending any data to the cloud, for privacy reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
